hey everyone caffeine man here and as
you can tell by the title of this video
i have an
extra special super hot highly talked
about new energy drink on the market
bonus review for you coming right up
hello again everyone thank you so much
for joining me today and if you want to
stay informed on all things caffeine
related feel free to hit the subscribe
button i post new videos every tuesday
night
and most friday nights and in today's
video we're going over two
brand new energy drinks from ghost
energy there are four cans total i only
have two cans right now
and a very big thank you to dan lorenko
the ceo of ghost
for sending me these drinks to try out
heard a lot of great things about them
and super excited to taste them out and
what can you guys expect from this video
if it's your first time here i do have a
tendency to talk a lot so i do use time
stamps
i am first gonna tell you a little bit
about ghost as a company
then i am definitely gonna go over the
incredible ingredients
in these drinks followed by a taste test
of two of their four flavors
time stamps down below so you can go
where you want to go because you like
missing out on important information
skippers ghost was started in 2016
only four years ago has become massively
successful when it came out it had a
pre-workout powder called ghost legend
which also had some additional focus
ingredients and two other products they
came out
at the same time were ghost amino and
ghost whey protein the two founders of
ghosts are ryan hughes
and dan lorenko ryan who went to
westchester university of pennsylvania
majored in business management and
marketing in leeds ghost marketing
efforts with a strong eye for brand
design
and a focus on social media with all of
his experience from being a sponsored
athlete
all the way to starting his own business
he's fit he understands
the health and fitness industry from
every angle dan lorenko is the ceo of
ghost but he didn't first start out in
the fitness business industry he was
actually into
aeronautical science which revolves
around the design and development of
aircraft
and even flying planes that's right he's
a pilot
and he actually helped angel flight as
part of the relief missions
in response to the earthquakes in haiti
in january of 2010.
he transported volunteer medical staff
medical devices
bandages water and non-perishable food
and with this flying experience
it's almost like he was destined to be
the ceo of ghost
you know because it goes fly
anyway for one reason or another he
decided to get into marketing and worked
his way up to vice president
of marketing at nutribol nutribull owned
cellycore the makers of c4
and extend after gaining valuable
experience there he and ryan hughes
decide to start ghost and i think that
dan volunteering at angelflight shows
that it's just in his nature to help
people and he's bringing that same
mentality to ghost with him
by trying to help people get the best
ingredients they can
from his product now even though ghost
is considered pre-workout their regular
pre-workout powders
actually have a decent amount of focus
ingredients as well when it comes to
these cans that they developed
they're actually focusing a little bit
more on those nootropic ingredients
so these drinks can be great for working
out but it could also be great for
gamers
as well as well basically anyone with
the ingredients that they put
in this can everyone will be able to get
the benefits of it whether they're
working out
working around the house hours of gaming
or even studying for school
it's definitely one of the things that i
love about nootropic ingredients
is that they give you usable energy that
helps you focus
and since this drink is for everybody
they're going to be doing everything in
their power to get this into your hands
because they've partnered with
anheuser-busch
for distribution and they are known for
having an amazing distribution network
so these drinks will be
into people's hands pretty quick once
it's fully released another great thing
about ghost as a company is that they
believe in full transparency they're
going to tell you about all the dosages
in their products and we're not just
talking about these cans even their
regular pre-workout powders they want
full transparency so that you know what
you're getting so let's take a look
what we're getting in these cans first
let's do a quick rundown of the
nutrition facts panel
one serving per can love it only five
calories
30 milligrams of sodium one just one
one itty-bitty pesky carbohydrate in
this thing
listen keto people it's just one gram of
carbs
carb one carb one gram of carbs one gram
of carbs it's just one
you can fit it into your diet do it it's
got lots of zeros it's got zero fat
zero cholesterol zero sugar zero protein
enough zeros let's get on to the 100 it
has 100
of all these things that i'm about to
list yeah each one of these things i
list 100
of your vitamin c folate biotin thiamin
that's your b1
niacin that's your b3 panthenic acid
which is your b5
as well as b6 and b12 100 of all
those things i just listed that's a lot
of 100
let's take a look at some of these
ingredients acetyl-l-carnitine also
known as alcar
is another type of carnitine l-carnitine
itself
plays a crucial role in the production
of energy and helps boost the metabolism
to help you burn calories
studies have shown that in addition to
helping the body produce energy
carnitine can also help boost endurance
it is important for heart and brain
function as well as muscle movement
alcar itself being a different type of
carnitine also has the added benefit
that it can cross the brain blood
barrier and therefore helps the body
deliver energy to the brain and central
nervous system
so there you go your very first
pre-workout ingredient
great for the body great for the brain
too but but
what's an effective dose of alcohol
anywhere between 500 milligrams
and 2 000 milligrams are considered to
be effective and even higher doses are
given
to help those with brain disorders most
people in general that supplement
with alcar will get the benefits from as
little as 500 milligrams
and these drinks have 1000 milligrams so
you definitely get an
effective dose taurine i actually talk
about taurine in a bit more detail
in my our energy drinks bad for you
series so feel free to check that out
but for now tauri's actually used in a
decent amount of energy drinks
because has been shown to help reduce
waste products that lead to fatigue
and cause muscle burn although it
doesn't specifically give you energy
it helps reduce fatigue and some people
consider that sort of like gaining
energy
just by default but touring has been
shown to have plenty of health benefits
such as lower risk of cardiovascular
disease and several improvements in
athletic performance including muscle
fatigue
but what's a good dosage people who
supplement with taurine regularly to
help with athletic performance
range between 500 milligrams and 3 000
milligrams per day to be effective
these drinks got a thousand milligrams
definitely effective dose two for two
alpha gpc alpha gpc is a very special
nutrient that has been shown to
significantly increase
acetylcholine levels in your brain in
turn this can help improve key brain
functions
such as memory concentration learning
recall
and focus one of the biggest benefits of
alpha gpc
is that it has this interesting thing
that it does called mind to muscle
where it boosts muscular output sharpens
agility
and also delays mental fatigue what's a
minimal effective dose
the minimal effective dose is between
250 and 500 milligrams
and these drinks use 150 milligrams so
it's just a little bit just a little bit
short you guys got to get just 100
milligrams more in there
and you'll be at that effective dose but
you know at 150
it's got to be doing something for you
but both the medical websites say
250 is better next up is neuro factor
neural factor is a registered trademark
ingredient and can you guess what it
does
it's used to help with brain functions
if you couldn't figure out by the word
neuro
it actually comes from coffee fruit
extract which is known to help boost
bdnf brain derive neurotropic factor
which helps you learn faster
increase mental clarity and focus and
since it's high in polyphenols it can
help fight inflammation
it is basically super food for your
brain an effective dose
is 100 milligrams these drinks 100
milligrams
estrogen estrogen is a patented 100
natural compound created by combining
astrogallus and ginseng and it increases
absorption of many
vital nutrients absorbing nutrients more
efficiently
can lead to improved physical
performance as well as overall health
additionally it is very useful in
promoting a healthy gut environment
good for your tumtum the recommended
dosage
the first few websites i looked at said
that it was about 50 milligrams but but
those were from supplement websites so
of course they want you to buy more but
as i dug deeper
i did find some healthy websites without
their own agenda that said the minimum
effective dose is 25 milligrams
these drinks you got it 25 milligrams
last but certainly not least the most
important one
of all cavine 200 milligrams of caffeine
loving it loving even more that is
natural caffeine
why do i love natural caffeine so much
natural caffeine takes a little bit
longer for the body to process
which is perfectly fine that it's a
little bit slower because it gives you
a longer lasting caffeine as some of you
know i think that 300 milligrams of
caffeine
is way too much for anyone to be taking
in unless they're working
out that's why they're called
pre-workout drinks the problem becomes
when
everyday people are drinking bang
they're drinking rain the gamers are
drinking g
fuel and they're taking far too much
caffeine into their system in my opinion
just my opinion because it wasn't that
long ago
that your standard energy drink and they
still do have 160 milligrams of caffeine
in them and that gives you more than
enough energy
those pre-workout drinks with 300 just
have way too much
therefore i love love love the fact that
ghosts decided to use
200 milligrams for their pre-workout if
you actually do
research there are actually medical
websites that say
200 milligrams is the perfect amount of
caffeine for working out and because
medical science
has actually proven that there are
companies that go with 200 milligrams
such as c4
america 3d celsius alanine
and several more including ghosts it
also means that you can have two a day
without going over your maximum 400 per
day all right guys it's time
let's taste it out first one up we're
gonna be going for the tropical mango
and by the way these cans are really
really nice they're all textured
and they have like a gloss finish and a
matte finish and they're actually
raised up so you can like feel the logo
and feel the ghost and
it's just it gives you a nice grip and
of course vibrant colors
just a great packaging job altogether
let's taste it out
all right oh yeah okay yeah i'm liking
it
all right so uh the carbonation you're
getting like a medium carbonation out of
there i don't think it's really hitting
medium high
and uh in the sweetness i was gonna say
it was like a medium sweetness but then
it started traveling a bit started
speeding up and it went to like medium
high pretty fast and
i think it might actually be high uh it
took a few seconds but i think it's
gonna be one of those things where it
stacks up a little bit so
i'm definitely definitely so i'm
definitely gonna have to go in for a
little bit more
but uh first impression yeah you get a
little bit of tropical then you get this
little bit of mango feel to it
and um it's not like overly tropical
they're not like
punching you with that pineapple and
other tropical flavors that
you're used to they're just giving you
this subtle hint of tropical and then
the mango kind of comes in and hits you
with some flavor
so i'm going to say the flavor profile
is a medium to high flavor profile so
it's not
punching you with flavor right away it's
giving you a nice solid flavor
and almost kind of a light flavor i'm
gonna go back in for that second sip to
see what flavors are gonna stack
did i say sip
yeah okay it's definitely going to be a
stacking effect i go in for that second
time i am getting a bit more tropical i
am getting a bit
citrus out of there now i didn't get too
much citrus at first
i'm just getting a hint more so
everything is starting to amplify itself
a little bit
so and that sweetness is definitely a
high sweetness now so yeah
i'm gonna actually say flavor profile is
a medium to high flavor profile but uh
it's really knocking on the door up high
with that sweetness going up and it's
really that sweetness is pulling out the
mango a little bit more too so i would
say when you first sip it you're getting
that tropical feel to it but then as you
drink it a little bit more
you're probably getting like a 65 to 70
mango flavor out of it
with that tropical complementing it so
where's it going to be going on the
caffeine man rating chart
i am going to give this a 9.1 extremely
solid flavor
very good very impressed with it it's
their first energy drink can line that
they're coming out with and they are
putting their best foot forward they're
giving you a really good tropical mango
moving on next up we're going with the
sour patch kids red berry
very excited about this one great
looking can great graphics on here
they've done a lot of stuff with the
yellow the red the black great colors to
complement each other i mean you can't
go wrong
with those colors but once again you got
the grip on there you got the feel
you got the little sour patch kids on
here and a lot of companies have done
sour drinks and they've actually done a
play
on the sour patch kids but this is an
actual sponsorship
and collaboration with sour patch kids
so you know
it's gotta be good two huge companies
ghost sour patch kids
red berry come on some people say they
like the lemon sour pat some people say
the green but but
but everyone knows red's the best and
i'm excited by it because i used to not
really be much of a sour
energy drink person but a lot of the
companies have been coming out with
these sweet and sour when you get that
sweet and sour combo
there's a really good job i've actually
been very impressed by several of the
sour flavors that actually
are sweet as well let's see how this one
goes
let's taste it out
[Music]
wow i can smell it from here it's been a
while since that happened get those
strong smells oh my goodness i'm going
to go in for a closer sniff now
that smells pretty good
here we go got the sweet got the sour
going on
got the red going on oh my goodness whoa
you know i gotta tell ya that's fun when
you have a drink that you start to drink
and then you're waiting to see what's
gonna happen and then all this stuff
it's like a party in your mouth going on
just all this stuff starts happening
it's like oh this is pretty good oh this
tastes kind of red berryish and this
kind of tastes
sweet a little oh there's the sour oh my
goodness i'm going back in for more
partying
don't mind me there's a party going on
over here oh party in my mouth
whoop oh police are here break up the
party kids don
sour patch kids partying might be sour
when the police show up
but but you know deep down there sweet
there's more in here
all right guys let's put this down so i
don't actually refill it
um that is that's really amazing stuff
that is basically
sour patch kids in liquid form you are
getting a sweet you're getting sour
you're getting all the stuff okay so
carbonation medium carbonation uh i
don't think it went the route of medium
high carbonation
and even if it did you can barely even
tell where the carbonation is because
the flavors are so strong
definitely a high sweetness definitely a
high flavor profile
and like i said when i was babbling
about the flavor and stuff
you basically are getting this red berry
flavor i mean that's called red berry
but you're getting this red almost like
a cherry strawberry kind of a mix of all
your different red berries
and you're really getting that red
flavor from the sour patch kid so i'm
not even gonna compare it you know
to all those other fruits and stuff
because those other fruits
are all put into the sour patch kid
candy and then they put it into this
drink
so it's making my job easy i don't have
to go into too much detail because it's
liquid sour patch kid really
the red one everyone's favorite
lime get out of here but yeah so and not
only am i gonna say that it has a high
flavor profile
and it has a high sweetness i'm also
gonna say it has a pretty high
sour flavor to it as well i mean just
like the candy you eat it you get that
sour on your mouth
and then you get the sweetness and
that's
and that's just
sour patch kids in a can 100 percent
not going to talk about it anymore
because there's nothing else to say
except it's delicious and time to put it
on the caffeine man rating chart
my goodness wow so yeah um
i'm actually compared to some other ones
i was a big fan of the g
fuel sour cherry i thought they did a
good job with their sour cherry i was
also a big fan of the g-fuel
sour chug rug because that was a kind of
like a kind of like a sweet and sour
blue razz
and even c4 did a c4 sour batch brothers
that was a lime flavor and you know some
people like lime and everything
not usually my favorite but they did a
good job with that overall
out of all of those and any of the
others sours that i've had
this one is the best one 100
replicates the candy flavor in a can so
accuracy with the drink and the flavor
is an amazing flavor so i am going to
put this
on the caffeine man rating chart
yeah i'm going to give this a 9.8
boom this is an amazing drink i mean you
gotta like your sweet and sour drinks
first of all
if you like sweet and you like sour it's
appealing to both target audiences
on the flavor spectrum you got your
sours you got your sweets then you got
everything in between
this is hitting both of those targets
this is going to be a drink for
everybody and i like this more than some
of the bangs out there
i like it more than some of the rains
out there i think this is a top-notch
drink
very sweet very sour very red
9.8 great job to ghost i cannot wait
to get the other two flavors that
they're they're they're looking into
sending me the other two flavors as well
but but they're very
very very popular so they're running out
so thank you very much to dan
at ghost for sending me these and thank
you to everyone at ghost for making
these
because they are some delicious flavors
they are in the process of being
released right now
some of them are online they've been
selling out really fast but once they
get that production going i expect them
to be selling out in stores
and hopefully they can keep up with
supply and demand online because
once once people start drinking that
they're going to be selling out of that
one too
i could add some more
drinking it from the cans even better
yes clear cups
that's all i got for you thank you so
much for joining me today i hope you
like this review let me know in a
comment down below what you thought of
this video and which one
you're looking forward to the most until
next time have yourselves a great day
or night
estrogen is a patented 100 natural
estrogen is a 100 patented natural
compound
estrogen is a 100 natural
is he patented estrogen is a patented
100 natural compound created by
combining astrology
created by created by combining
astragalus
astragalus created by created by
combining astragalus and ginseng
and it increases absorption and it
increases absorption
of many vital nutrients
you